signnow.com 2017-09-03

# Barracuda Networks Privacy Policy - Barracuda Networks

We recognize and respect your right to privacy. This policy explains how Barracuda Networks (Barracuda) collects and handles data. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your data and how we will treat it.

## Types of Information

  * Personal Information is information that enables us to identify you, such as your email address, name, mailing address, telephone number, company name, and credit card information.

  * Your Information is information you store in, or transfer to, any of our products or services, whether or not it is Personal Information.

## How We Protect Information

Barracuda Networks is committed to taking steps to protect the Information you provide to us, including administrative, technical, and physical measures — to safeguard Information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. 

Information is accessed only by authorized staff who are instructed to handle Information with confidentiality. It is protected by firewalls and standard industry security measures. We may also transmit sensitive information and transactional data using secure socket layer (SSL) encryption. 

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect Information, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received Information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access. 

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our website site or our products and services, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone. 

## How We Use Information

We use the Information you supply in the following ways:

  * to register you for webinars/seminars.

  * to assign a password.

  * to ensure that content from our website and services are presented in the most efficient manner for you. 

  * to provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.

  * to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.

  * to allow you to participate in interactive features, such as “Live Chat”, when you choose to do so.

  * to notify you about changes to our products or services.

  * to take other action you request when you supply the Information.

  * To provide the service(s) you have requested

## Sharing Information With Third Parties and Within Barracuda

We do not sell, hire, lease or rent the personal information we collect to anyone at this time. Unless we have your permission, are required by law, are required to do so in order to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements with you or are required to do so to protect the rights, property or safety of Barracuda, our customers or others, we will only provide personal information to other Barracuda entities within our group, and to third parties who assist Barracuda operate our websites, resell our products or services, or help us with some products or services we provide. Data provided to third parties is stored on systems we do not own and is provided in accordance with our policies. 

In addition, we may disclose your personal information to third parties (i) in the event we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your Personal Information to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets; or (ii) if Barracuda or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case Information held by it about its customers and partners will be one of the transferred assets. 

We may transfer your information across border and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. The data we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored in the United States or another destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). It may also be processed by staff operating in the United States or otherwise outside the EEA. Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of services. By submitting your Information, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. 

## Your Control over Information

When you register for an account or submit Information to Barracuda , we will occasionally contact you via email, postal mail, or telephone. This contact may involve notification of new services being offered by Barracuda. You may opt-out of this contact by deactivating your account. If you no longer wish to maintain an account with Barracuda Networks, please go to our contact us at [ webmaster ](mailto:webmaster@barracudanetworks.com) and we will remove you from our contacts list. 

In addition, you have the right to access Information held about you. Please visit our Contact Information page or email webmaster for more details.

##  Use of the Barracuda Websites:

#### Personal Information Collected:

You may use most of our websites without supplying any personal information. However, sites or certain parts of a site are available only if you obtain a password. Barracuda Networks collects personal information when you register for a password, and at various other places on our site where you may register for a webinar/seminar or obtain or request other information or services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our site. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. We may also collect personal information when you carry out a payment transaction through our site, request an evaluation or enter into “Live Chat” via the site.

In addition, we automatically log the domain name of where you came from, the IP address your computer is currently using, the type of web browser that you use, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring and exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. This information allows us to improve the site by serving the pages you visit, and we may use the information for statistical purposes and to track usage patterns. In addition, we use the data we collect to make various determinations in our systems. We do not use this information to personally identify you, the user. 

#### Use of Cookies

Barracuda Networks uses cookies for your convenience to store information so you do not have to reenter your data upon each visit. Cookies and other technology are also used to monitor usage of the various features and services of our site, which over time gives us information to improve our site, and to advertise and market our products more effectively. To view the types of cookies Barracuda uses on its websites, please [ click here ](https://www.barracuda.com/assets/docs/dms/CookiesForWebsites.xlsx) .

When you visit our websites, cookies will be placed on your computer or device. To maximize your experience and to help us understand how we can improve our site. If you prefer not to receive cookies, you can set your browser to either reject all cookies, to allow “trusted” sites to set them, or to accept only those cookies from those sites you are currently on. However turning off cookies will hinder your ability to access, use, or navigate portions of the site. 

#### Links to Other Sites

Our site contains links to other sites. If you choose to visit any of those sites then their privacy policies would apply. The Barracuda Privacy Policy applies solely to the information collected from the Barracuda web site. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for third party policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal information to these websites. 

## Changes In This Policy

If we change the way we use your personal information we will post the change here on our web site. We recommend that you regularly visit this page to learn of any changes. The change will apply to information our users furnish after the change, and information we have on file for existing users.

If you have any questions regarding this policy or our use of personally identifiable information on this site, please send us your questions or comments to [ webmaster ](mailto:webmaster@barracudanetworks.com) .

Last Updated: June 2016
